Spencer Wong

Selangor, Malaysia



spenwong98@gmail.com



0143192028



linkedin.com/in/spencer-wong-8946b6127

Summary

I am a young Front-end web developer who was always adventurous on learning new coding skills and experiences. I graduated in 2021 with a Computer Science degree, currently working as a Front-end web developer. I have industrial working experience in building websites. The programming languages that I have experience are JavaScript, HTML, CSS and PHP. I am currently improving my JavaScript skill by learning ReactJS framework, and hope to implement the skill and knowledge into real-life project.

Experience

FOREFRONT Intern

FOREFRONT International (FOREFRONT)

Dec 2020 - Mar 2021 (4 months)

- During my internship, I am responsible to help develop a website for Sunway Money along with my supervisor.
- This is my first time working in the web development field, and I have gained a lot of experience working along with my supervisor and other colleagues.

HURERONT UX Developer

FOREFRONT International (FOREFRONT)

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year +)

Responsibility:

- Help to maintain existing website
- Work closely with UI designer to deliver a UI/UX friendly website

Skills:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, Jekyll, Docker, Gulp, Webpack

Impact:

- I have successfully developed more than 5 different websites in a year with Forefront International

Education

Sunway University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Aug 2018 - Aug 2021



Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Aug 2019 - Jul 2021

Skills

 $\mbox{HTML} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf Bootstrap} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf JavaScript} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf PHP} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf SCSS} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf jQuery} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf MordPress} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf Adobe XD} \ \ \mbox{\bf \bullet} \ \mbox{\bf Figma}$